fanoos.com 2014-11-29

# Fanoos Privacy

Fanoos takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. Also, please read our Children's Privacy Policy to learn more about how we treat personally identifiable information collected from children and Privacy Information to learn how we treat such information collected in connection with Fanoos financial products and services. 

This Privacy Policy covers both Fanoos and Middle East Links treatment of personally identifiable information that Fanoos collects when you are on Fanoos, and when you use our services.  
This policy also covers Fanoos treatment of any personally identifiable information that Fanoos business partners share with Fanoos or that Fanoos or Middle East Links may collect on a partner's site.   
This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Fanoos or Middle East Links does not own or control, or to people that Fanoos does not employ or manage. 

**INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE**  
Both Fanoos and Middle East Links collects personally identifiable information when you register for any of our accounts, when you use certain Fanoos products or services, when you visit Fanoos pages, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. Fanoos or Middle East Links may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners.   
When you register with Fanoos, we ask for your name, email address, birth date, gender, occupation, industry, and personal interests. Once you register with Fanoos and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.   
Fanoos also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, Fanoos cookie information and the page you requested.  
Fanoos uses such information for three general purposes mainly: to customize the advertising and content you see, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, and to contact you about specials and new products. 

**INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE**  
Fanoos will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone.  
Fanoos may send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when:   
We have your consent to share the information;   
We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested;   
We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of Fanoos or Middle East Links to provide a product or service to you. (Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us.);  
We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or   
We find that your actions on our web sites violate Fanoos Terms of Service, Middle East Links Terms of Service, or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services. 

**COOKIES**  
Fanoos may set and access Fanoos cookies on your computer.   
Fanoos allows other companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Fanoos cookies.   
Fanoos uses web beacons to access our cookies within and outside our network of web sites and in connection with Fanoos products and services.  

**ACCOUNT MODIFICATIONS AND PREFERENCES**  
Fanoos gives you the ability to edit your Fanoos Account Information and preferences at any time, including whether you want Fanoos to contact you about specials and new products.  
You may request deletion of your Fanoos account by visiting our Account Deletion page, verifying your password once more and confirming your choice to terminate the account. 

**SECURITY**  
Your Fanoos Account Information is password-protected for your privacy and security.   
In certain areas Fanoos uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions.

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**  
Fanoos may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.

**QUESTIONS AND SUGGESTIONS**  
If you have questions or suggestions complete a feedback form.   
Fanoos and Middle East certification applies to all English-language, French-language and Arabic-language sites including LebanonLinks.com, MELinks.com, LebanonLinks.com.lb, LebanonLinks.net domains. If you feel that your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact our quality of service department. 

**GOOGLE and DART**  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
